JENNIFER WEAVER

10533 S. Sage Flats Way, South Jordan, UT 84009 Ph. 385-329-3558 * Email: jnnfrwvr@yahoo.com

COMMUNICATIONS I PUBLIC RELATIONS I MEDIA RELATIONS

QUALIFICATIONS PROFILE

I have been in communications/marketing and print/TV management for more than 25 years. I am an award-winning journalist with advertising sales and digital experience. I've just completed certification in web development and design from SLCC.

CORE COMPETENCIES

- Illustrator CC Level 1 Certificate
- Blog writing & editing
- Fluent in AP Style
- Google Docs & MS Word
- Adobe PhotoShop
- Video Editing
- Promo & Animoto
- Whiteboard Animation
- Email Marketing

- Sprout Social, Crowdtangle
- Facebook, Twitter, Instagram
- YouTube, Pinterest, Reddit, LinkedIn
- Tumblr, Beebe, Medium
- Zoom,TEAMS,WebEx
- InDesign
- HTML, CSS, JS, MySQL, Bootstrap
- Google Analytics
- Google AdWords PPC

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

CHOLANGIOCARCINOMA FOUNDATION

DIRECTOR OF COMMUNICATIONS

June 14, 2021 to PRESENT

- Establish and drive a comprehensive, multi-channel communications strategy.
- Improve stakeholder outreach and information sharing through effective use of website, newsletters, social networking, and public relations.
- With the collaboration of teammates, prepare and manage the creation of all communication content, including print, video, audio, and digital materials for general purposes, fundraising, advocacy, and research.
- Manage and safeguard the Cholangiocarcinoma Foundation brand.
- Manage media relations, including the development of contacts with media members, influencers, and community leaders, and the creation of media toolkit and press releases, briefs, and other media focused materials.
- Work collaboratively and build relationships with the marketing, communications, and public relations teams of trusted partners, industry, and other organizations within the Cholangiocarcinoma community.
- Lead a team of communication, marketing, design professionals, and volunteers.
- Track engagement across various platforms and make data-driven decisions, including reporting and analysis of online and social media activities.

- Manage the Foundation's presence at industry events, medical meetings, and conferences, including the materials and resources.
- Manage a budget for the communications team and ensure compliance.

KUTV 2NEWS

EXECUTIVE PRODUCER OF DIGITAL NEWS Nov.13, 2017 to PRESENT

- Develop and implement a digital content strategy for KUTV.com and 2News app
- Work with West Region stations of Sinclair Broadcast Group & AP for syndication
- Manage a staff of six and work closely with assignment desk, reporters
- Make sure KUTV broadcast and digital staff are working together to increase ratings and digital/mobile/social stats.
- Copy-edit and write stories for online and on Amazon Alexa.
- Administer all social media platforms of KUTV; Facebook, Twitter, Instagram, YouTube, Reddit, Pinterest, LinkedIn
- Daily News Alert Email using SecondStreet

FOREVERGREEN INTERNATIONAL

COMMUNICATIONS & MARKETING MANAGER May 5, 2016- Nov. 10, 2017

- Communications Corporate press releases
- Investor Relations
- Email Marketing Campaigner and Campaign Monitor
- Zoom conferencing training
- Livestreaming
- Social media management and posts
- Scriptwriting for video
- Product promotion, branding, description, labeling and packaging

BLENDFRESH

COMMUNICATIONS & MARKETING MANAGER April 2016 – March 25, 2017

- Communications Policy & Guidelines Manual, 16-page & 20-page magazine, recipe book, shopper guide, training materials, business cards, press releases, flyers, social media posts.
- Editorial Content Calendar for Social Media Sprout Social
- Video Editing Adobe Premiere, Splice, Quicktime, Promo & Animoto
- Graphic Design social media posts, booklets, trainings, magazine using Adobe InDesign, Illustrator and PhotoShop
- Website Administration WordPress Blogs, SEO (Yoast plug-in)
- Email Marketing MailChimp
- Whiteboard Animation RawShorts and VideoScribe
- Trade Shows TechMunch, Everything Food Conference, FitCon
- Affiliate and Online Outreach for brand influencers

NU SKIN ENTERPRISES, INC.

- Public Relations FAQ sheets, PIPs, Media outreach, press releases, CSR quarterly and annual reports, website administration using Adobe CQ4, crisis management, social media
- Editorial Calendar Shoutlet and Adobe Suite for online content
- Industry News and Media Coverage Excel and PowerPoints
- Graphic design –banner ads and memes
- Write and submit award applications on behalf of the company and its products
- Event planning global convention, Sub-for-Santa, annual day of service, etc.

KSTU FOX 13

ASSIGNMENT MANAGER

November 2011 — April 2014

- Monitor media outlets from multi-sources to ensure content for 9 hours of news
- Supervise staff of three assignment editors
- Story assignment to photographers and reporters for coverage of all news broadcasts
- Create long-term planning and set-up of sources for sweeps pieces and other enterprise stories
- Research and confirmation of information, including filing GRAMA and FOIA requests
- Associate Producing and Digital Producing

THE SPECTRUM & CEDAR CITY DAILY NEWS

BUREAU CHIEF 2001 - 2011

BEAT: Iron County, Utah Shakespeare Festival, Southern Utah University, health/medical, public education, social issues. Also, was first female Opinion Page Editor in the state of Utah.

- Supervise staff and edit work of three reporters: sports and general reporting
- Write columns twice a week and general reporting
- Site administrator of SouthernUtah.MomsLikeMe.com
- Content management and assignments for weekly16-page tabloid
- Budget and administer expenses of reporters
- Blog and critique the newspaper weekly
- Post and create poll question for website weekly
- Created editorial policy/Editor/Opinion Page Editor
- Event planning such as political debates, symposiums and workshops

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF PHOENIX

Masters in Public Administration/Management GPA 3.76 - Lambda Sigma Chapter of the International Business Honor Society, Delta Mu Delta.

UNIVERSITY OF UTAH, Salt Lake City, Utah Bachelor of Science, Human Development and Family Studies *Transfer Student Leadership Scholarship

SALT LAKE COMMUNITY COLLEGE, Salt Lake City, Utah

General Education with emphasis in Communications
*Leadership Scholarship

SPECIAL TRAINING

Leadership Dixie, 2006

CHIP/Medicaid Training, Feb. 2001

Mediation Training, University of Utah, Spring 1997

Train the Trainer," State of Utah, 1998

Swanson Foundation Grant Writing Training

Background Criminal Investigations/Fingerprint Training, Utah Bureau of Criminal

Identification, February, 1998; and re-certified by the Weber County Sheriff's Dept., Sgt.

Klint Anderson, January 1999

Program Outcome Evaluations Training – Utah Mentor Network, 1999

Gang Prevention, Intervention & Suppression Training (15 hours), April, 1999

AWARDS & ACHIEVEMENTS

Edward R. Murrow Awards Judge for Multimedia and Social Media Excellence AP Best Editorial of the Year

Don Baker Award for Investigative Reporting

Associated Press: Utah-Spokane-Washington - 1st Place Breaking News, 3rd Place Editorial

Gannett Well Done – Runner Up for First Amendment Investigative Reporting

Utah Champions Award for Media

SPJ Awards – Numerous First Place for Spot News, Personality Profile, Features

Ms. American Majesty 2003

Mrs. Utah Achievement 2001-2002

Ms. Western US States Universal Woman 2001-2002

Mrs. Utah National Achiever

Northern District "Young Careerist, 2001" Business & Professional Women

First Runner-Up, State of Utah BPW - "Young Careerist of the Year"

Utah Children Advocacy Academy - KIDS Count Leader, 2001-2002

6th Annual Alpha Award Nominee - National Job Corp

Certificate of Recognition and Red Wagon Plaque for contributions to "Utah's Promise"

Presenter at the 3rd Annual Western United States Student Assisting Conference

Ogden BPW, "Young Careerist of the Year," February 1998

Who's Who in American Junior Colleges - two years in a row, 1989-90

Outstanding College Activities Board Member, SLCC, Public Relations, 1989

Utah Mentor Network - Training Committee

LEADERSHIP

Women of Worth Utah, Inc. – Advisory Board Member

Society of Professional Journalists – Utah Headliners Board Member

United Way of Iron County - Chair

America's Promise of Iron County - Chair

Utah's Promise Chair - Clearfield City

Clearfield Community Council

United Way Volunteer Advisory Council

Davis County Community of Promise

Davis County Child Abuse Prevention Team
Davis County SAFE KIDS Coalition
START Committee
Cedar City Rotary – Sgt. At Arms & Secretary
Youth of Promise Committee
Governor's Commission on Marriage
Clearfield Job Corp Community Relations Council
Family Enrichment Center Advisory Council
Iron County United Way - President
Families Agencies Communities Together (FACT)
Iron County Relay for Life – Luminaria Chair
Asset Based Community Development Committee 4-H Youth Advisory Council member

Vice President - Lakeview Business & Professional Women's Club